{
    "id": "eef15873a59b40c5b50a7a6add4b9b2d",
    "title": "Although, But, So And Because",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "46826e75fb564a1db1cb8f38fcfca67b",
            "title": "Although, But, So And Because",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "....................................... I like him I don't want to spend every evening with him.",
                    "description": "We use although to connect two contrasting ideas. It is a subordinating conjunction and usually goes at the beginning of the clause. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Although",
                        "But",
                        "Because"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She liked him ......................................... she did not want to marry him.",
                    "description": "But is a coordinating conjunction. It has more or less the same meaning as although but it is used to connect two clauses of equal rank. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "although",
                        "but",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": ".......................................... John had more years of experience than Peter, he did not get the promotion.",
                    "description": "We use although to connect two contrasting ideas. It is a subordinating conjunction and usually goes at the beginning of the clause. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Although",
                        "But",
                        "Because"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She wanted to go on holiday ........................................ she was short of money.",
                    "description": "But is a coordinating conjunction. It has more or less the same meaning as although but it is used to connect two clauses of equal rank. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "although",
                        "but",
                        "because"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................................ few people participated in the program, it was a commercial success.",
                    "description": "We use although to connect two contrasting ideas. It is a subordinating conjunction and usually goes at the beginning of the clause. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Although",
                        "But",
                        "Because"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I did not understand a thing .......................................... I said nothing.",
                    "description": "But is a coordinating conjunction. It has more or less the same meaning as although but it is used to connect two clauses of equal rank. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "although",
                        "but",
                        "because"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": ".......................................... I find it relaxing, I often go to movies.",
                    "description": "We use because to introduce the reason for something. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Although",
                        "But",
                        "Because"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................................... she was short of money she could not buy the ticket.",
                    "description": "We use because to introduce the reason for something. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Although",
                        "Because",
                        "So"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................................... I love him, I always support him.",
                    "description": "We use because to introduce the reason for something. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Because",
                        "Although",
                        "But"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The last bus had gone .............................................. we had to walk home.",
                    "description": "We use so to introduce the result or effect of the action mentioned in the previous clause. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "although",
                        "because",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was upset ................................................ he said nothing.",
                    "description": "We use so to introduce the result or effect of the action mentioned in the previous clause. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "although",
                        "because",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................................... he is a foreigner he cannot find a job easily.",
                    "description": "We use because to introduce the reason for something. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Because",
                        "Although",
                        "So"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}